You mean you really don't remember our group, Sakura?
I don't.
See, you're kind of a zombie.
Does this mean she can't be in the show?
But when the time comes, I know you'll be ready.
No, I can't do it.
It's like the world punishes me for even trying.
You know damn well this isn't where you need to be.
If you want to do this idle thing, then go right ahead, but leave me out of it!
You don't know the first thing about me, because you've never died.
I have what it takes!
Listen to me!
I will never, and I mean never abandon you!
Hey, good morning!
Good morning to you.
What's up, what's up, what's up?
Oh, Sakura, I thought for sure you'd still be hungover from your big pity party, but here you are.
Good morning, sad sack!
Oh, jeez, watch those manners.
No one's gonna respect you without them.
I don't really care if people respect me or not.
Yeah, well, I do.
You can glare at me with those dead eyes all day long.
It won't change a thing.
You will be a part of this show.
This feels kind of familiar.
There's no way I can do it.
settings are terrible at all.
You'll be a part of this show.
Ah.
You're kind of scary.
We start practice at the same time tomorrow, just so you know.
And after that, we're going to go pass out flyers.
We'd love for you to come.
Here's the info.
Hope you'll be there.
What was I thinking coming here?
Number one.
Do you mind if I shake your hand?
Oh.
You're great.
Watching you sing and dance always makes me happy.
You inspire me so much.
I can hardly wait for Arpino.
We'll be cheering you on.
Wow, thanks, you two.
You're the best.
And I've seen your faces.
If you don't show, I'm going to come and hunt you down.
Number two.
We'll be there.
Do your best.
Right.
See you then.
Look at that.
You're pretty popular, aren't you?
Yeah.
Watching you sing and dance always makes me happy.
I wonder what my singing and dancing were like.
It's always the same story, though.
I get my hopes up.
Then I ruin everything and regret trying it all.
If I do this, I'll just bring them down with me.
Listen!
I swear I will never abandon you!
No, forget that.
There's no hope it'll work out.
I know that better than anyone else.
Leave me alone!
I don't care!
I knew we shouldn't have pushed her so hard.
Ah, damn it!
What are we going to do?
There's hardly any time left now.
Are we really going to have to go on stage without Sakura there?
Uh-huh.
I think she'll break it down?
I reinforced the door when I fixed it, so I don't think she can.
Oh, she's crying.
You're kidding!
Wait, I think that's drool.
Oh, man.
That can't be good.
Did being ignored give her attention withdrawal?
What is she doing?
It's me.
What's with you?
I think I understand.
Yeah, Sakura was never the type to half-ass it, was she?
Right, and she refused to give up.
When she helped her learn the routine, I bet it made Tai happy.
So that's why...
She's trying to teach Sakura this time.
When someone had a problem or kept messing up, she was the first one to jump in.
In her own awkward manner.
Thanks to all her encouragement, I conquered my fears of working in a group.
She was always willing to listen to my ideas.
So let's think of this as a chance to pay Sakura back.
I agree.
She needs her friends now more than ever.
We shouldn't let her down.
If we all try hard, I'm sure we'll think of something.
Yeah, sounds good.
This is what Team Franchu-shu is all about, right?
We've got each other's backs no matter what.
Okay, time for us to get your head on str...
I'm telling you, there's no point.
You guys are getting yourselves all excited over a bunch of stuff that I don't even remember
happening in the first place.
Well, good night.
That's enough.
I cannot let you run away any longer.
You've encouraged us till now, and you must see this through.
Whether you can remember anything or not, you're still going to join us on that stage.
Of all the selfish-
I'm fully aware that it's selfish.
I don't get why all of you care so much about me.
What difference does it make if I perform with you?
Just look at their faces.
We understand that you no longer have any memories, and that your luck may be bad.
But these are troubled times, Lady Sakura, and we need you.
Our sisterhood may be strong now, but without you holding us together, we would never have
gotten this far.
Lady Time made me see.
If the only way for the show to be a success is without you, then I would much rather the
seven of us fail together.
Please, try to understand that.
Sakura, you seem to think that you're the only one here with bad luck.
But let me remind you.
The rest of us are zombies too.
We all died.
There's not an ounce of good luck in this whole group.
I don't think of mistakes or failures as bad things.
That's not how it works.
They always end up helping me with whatever happens next.
If I want to be the best version of me, then I'll have to find a way over the hurdles.
Think about it, guys.
I could wind up turning this show into a full-on catastrophe.
As I said before, we are well aware.
And if something gets wrecked, Shades can deal with it.
See?
Problem solved.
Well, nice!
You've really got it down now!
I guess it's your muscle memory.
She did practice the most out of the whole group.
I knew it.
Sakura!
Huh?
Huh.
Now who's got bad luck?
That's how luck is.
It can change whenever people, or when zombies, work together.
But, you sure about this?
You all put so much into your show.
Yeah, so did you!
You were right there with us every step of the way!
We're in this for life.
Or afterlife.
Sakura.
We're going to do our best.
Because it's all we can do.
Are you in?
The explosive low-pressure cold front that developed over the East China Sea this morning is now headed directly toward Kyushu.
It's expected to reach northern Kyushu by tomorrow evening.
Please be prepared for heavy snowfall and make an effort to remain indoors as much as possible.
Oh, Inui!
Thank you!
Tonight is the night of the living people.
The living dead we've all been waiting for, Frans Shushu!
Let's show those 500 people, or however many show up, that zombies never die!
Right!
I say Saga's never had snow like this before.
Yeah, they've shut down the buses and everything.
These poor girls have the worst luck.
Thanks a lot!
Make sure to cheer nice and loud during the show!
This reminds me of when Iron Frill performed here.
Oh yeah, that was the last concert we put on.
I hope these Frans Shushu kids are good.
So do I.
We've put in the time.
All we can do now is give it our best shot.
So let's just focus on that.
We did great in practice.
Yeah, I guess so.
Snow is falling down, down.
Hail is falling down, down.
Well, duh, where else is it gonna fall?
It's chilly, but it's okay.
Just gotta be tough.
I wouldn't miss this for the world.
For a solo gig!
This storm better bugger off so they can rock the way.
Holy cow.
This is some turnout.
All your fans are waiting.
I believe in you.
Circle up, guys.
We'll be okay.
We've had tons of rehearsal time.
And we've got our team.
Let's have faith.
Awesome!
Time to go take over Saga!
Right!
Oh, no.
They traveled through all that terrible weather just to see us.
What if something really bad happens and I screw the whole thing up?
Here we go, Artina!
Love to have ya!
Can't stop what I'm feeling.
Running away with BB.
Now I'm stuck.
Don't stop.
Gotta push through.
Don't forget what's inside you.
Put on a smile, it's okay.
Life goes on, though we decay.
Stop the show right now!
We're on it!
Wait.
Have they now lost their allure?
We can't go back for the time.
Move ahead.
Don't look back.
Even if you might lose your way.
You stray!
I don't see you.
Leave you.
Let me.
Letěje ta Marcelo 53
We'll see you next time.
Don't know where my future will be enfin.
This episode is joined by this episode of Foto Negotiabmy.
I knew this would happen.
Thanks to me, everyone failed.
Time and time again, we'll rise up stronger than before.
Remember, every ending is the beginning.
It's up to you to find the door.
Life is so unfair that you gotta work through your despair.
Don't waste your time with asking why.
To all your fears, just say goodbye.
When you've been knocked down, don't ever forget.
If the only way for the show to be a success is without you,
then I would much rather the seven of us fail together.
I don't think of mistakes or failures as bad things.
That's not how it works.
I have what it takes!
Whether or not you have what it takes is irrelevant, because I do!
Answer their call, Sakura.
When you're up against a wall,
that's when your true strength shines.
You'll see.
You can rise again!
Hey, change of plans.
Are we back up yet?
Good to go!
No more hiding, let the lighten tear down every wall.
Suffering cannot be in fate if you use that pain deep inside to fuel you.
Torn and tethered, it doesn't matter.
You can be restored.
No giving up on all your dreams.
You have more power than you think.
Hold on to hope when you've been knocked down low.
And claw your way out!
I'll take it down and make you step closer.
Wait.
You have more power than others,
or wait!
Certain missed part,
an obsession
no Trailzus Любiton!
Hey!
I know!
Time and time again we'll rise up stronger than before
Remember every ending is a beginning
It's up to you to find the door
Life is so unfair but you've got a word for your despair
Don't waste your time with asking why
To all your fears just say goodbye
When you've been knocked down don't ever forget
You can rise again
What a thrill
Yay
One more song
Hey you seem different
Are your memories back?
Uh huh
Guys I'm really sorry for how I acted
It's fine
Damn you kicked ass out there
No wonder your moves were so sharp
It really was an incredible performance
Yes and it's so wonderful to have you back
Hey uh listen if you guys don't mind having me and all of my bad luck around
Can we go back to the way things were?
Don't be ridiculous Sakura
Sure we can
Thanks a lot
Stop right there
Jeez it's like the finale of some feel good friendship show
This ain't over yet you dumb zombies
You can't just stand there and rot
I mean you haven't even saved one square foot of Saga Prefecture
They came for a concert and that's what they're gonna get
Your battle's only just begun so march your butts back out there
Go go go go go yeah yeah yeah go go go go go go
Go go go go go
Yeah
Ready go
I feel the days come and pass me by
Can't get excited though I try
You don't want to waste your life like that
Do you though?
I can always feel as strong when blowing through
Blowing everywhere no matter what I do
Grab on to that breeze and hold on tight
Never let go!
Don't be shy
There's nothing to be so embarrassed about
Go boys and girls
You live only once
Don't take it down!
Let your flag fly high up in the sky
Riding on the air with all your hopes and your dreams
Let your voice be heard across the world tonight
Cause a new day is about to begin
And I have
And you have
Come so far in life
Let your flag fly high up in the sky
Hooray! Hooray! Let's go!
Look into the future and you'll see
You will make it
Hold your own pride and you will be
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray! Let's go!
There is no telling what could happen
What we'll see
The day we cross each other's paths and meet again!
Ready? Go!
Go!
Go!oo!
Shoot!
whoo!
Good morning!
Hey, there you are. So you happy with these pictures we got?
Uh, is something wrong?
Now I'm more confused.
The hell's going on with these girls?
I medio here.
My plan can be open.
And now subscribe to our channel.
Of course, Teksting Taylor vielmehr.
Nyah Pham, Brandagin Varun Centre,
patrons from have it be.
We give you across the region and see ya know all the different 1900s and many of these animals which,
you know, when it is in operation itself.
So, don't forget to hear them.